<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>isXander</title><link>https://www.isxander.dev/</link><description>Recent content on isXander</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.isxander.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Photography</title><link>https://www.isxander.dev/photography/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Apr 2023 20:16:16 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.isxander.dev/photography/</guid><description>I have started an instagram where I post new photos here.
My Current Equipment Link to heading Canon EOS R10 - I saved up £1000 of my own money to buy this in late 2022. RF-S 18-45mm F4.5-6.3 IS STM Kit DJI Air 2S - A photography drone that I use to take pictures I would never have been able to get before. Pixel 6 Pro - My camera for on-the-go.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://www.isxander.dev/about/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2023 13:22:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://www.isxander.dev/about/</guid><description>👋 I&amp;rsquo;m Xander Link to heading I create Minecraft mods using Java and Kotlin, I love doing what I&amp;rsquo;m doing. My mods are on GitHub, Curseforge and Modrinth. I occasionally do commission work for Minecraft mods if I see a request that particularly interests me or I feel like it will help further my learning and experiences. I have also tinkered with some statistical analysis and AI with Python.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.isxander.dev/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.isxander.dev/contact/</guid><description>Contact Me Link to heading There are many reasons you may want to contact me, but some questions/enquiries may be better answered on my public discord server. You can create user support threads or just ask in #general. For most things, this will be what you want.
Business Enquiries Link to heading If you&amp;rsquo;d like to do business with me you can either contact me through Discord private messages (@isxander) (where I will reply the fastest) or contact me through my business email.</description></item></channel></rss>